<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Fabform Blog</title><description>Welcome to FabForm</description><link>https://blog.fabform.io/</link><item><title>Build a Complete Astro Blog: From Template Setup to a Fully Functional Contact Form with Fabform</title><link>https://blog.fabform.io/blog/build-astro-blog-with-fabform-contact-form/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.fabform.io/blog/build-astro-blog-with-fabform-contact-form/</guid><description>Learn how to create a fast, modern static blog using the official Astro Blog template and enhance it with a fully working contact form powered by Fabform. This step‑by‑step guide covers setup, customization, form integration, and deployment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fabform vs Formspree: A Deep Comparison for Modern Static‑Site Builders</title><link>https://blog.fabform.io/blog/fabform-vs-formspree/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.fabform.io/blog/fabform-vs-formspree/</guid><description>A comprehensive, developer‑focused comparison of Fabform and Formspree. Covers setup, spam protection, file uploads, pricing models, Astro compatibility, and why Fabform’s one‑time payment model is changing the form‑backend landscape.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Netlify Forms Not Working? The Real Reason They Break (And the Fastest Fix for Static Sites)</title><link>https://blog.fabform.io/blog/netlify-forms-not-working-fix/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.fabform.io/blog/netlify-forms-not-working-fix/</guid><description>If your Netlify Forms aren’t working, you’re not alone. This deep-dive explains the hidden reasons Netlify Forms fail on Astro, Eleventy, Hugo, and other static-site frameworks—and shows the simplest, most reliable alternative.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Build an Astro Contact Form Without Serverless Functions (2026 Guide)</title><link>https://blog.fabform.io/blog/astro-contact-form-without-serverless/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.fabform.io/blog/astro-contact-form-without-serverless/</guid><description>A complete, developer‑focused guide to building a contact form in Astro without serverless functions, API routes, or backend code. Learn the simplest, fastest, and most reliable way to handle form submissions on any static host.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Netlify Forms Break (And the Best Alternatives for Static Sites in 2026)</title><link>https://blog.fabform.io/blog/netlify-forms-alternative-static-sites/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.fabform.io/blog/netlify-forms-alternative-static-sites/</guid><description>Netlify Forms often fail silently, require confusing configuration, and break on modern static-site workflows. This guide explains why—and shows the simplest, most reliable alternative for Astro, Eleventy, Hugo, and Cloudflare Pages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Build an Astro Site From a Template and Add a Working Fabform Contact Form</title><link>https://blog.fabform.io/blog/astro-template-with-fabform-contact/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.fabform.io/blog/astro-template-with-fabform-contact/</guid><description>Learn how to create a new Astro site from a template and integrate a fully functional Fabform contact form into your pages. No serverless functions, no backend code—just clean, modern static-site development.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Set Up a GitHub Pages Site with a Backendless Contact Form</title><link>https://blog.fabform.io/blog/add-serverless-contact-form-github-pages/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.fabform.io/blog/add-serverless-contact-form-github-pages/</guid><description>A complete beginner&apos;s guide to creating a GitHub Pages website and adding a backendless contact form using Fabform.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Set Up a Cloudflare Pages Site with a Backendless Contact Form</title><link>https://blog.fabform.io/blog/cloudflare-pages-contact-form-tutorial/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.fabform.io/blog/cloudflare-pages-contact-form-tutorial/</guid><description>Step-by-step beginner guide to creating a Cloudflare Pages website and adding a backendless contact form using Fabform.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Set Up a Netlify Site with a Backendless Contact Form</title><link>https://blog.fabform.io/blog/netlify-contact-form-tutorial/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.fabform.io/blog/netlify-contact-form-tutorial/</guid><description>Step-by-step guide for beginners to create a Netlify website and add a backendless contact form using Fabform.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>